shimano.co.jp 2006-06-15

# Shimano Corporate Site

SHIMANO GLOBAL PRIVACY POLICY

 **Welcome**  
Welcome! This site is owned by Shimano. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to this site. 

**Consent**  
By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy 

**Information Collected**  
In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. In addition, there are portions of this Web site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information you request or to conduct surveys and contests. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address. 

**Children**  
We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information via this site from visitors younger than 18. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to Web sites. 

**Use and Disclosure**  
Except as otherwise stated, we may use information collected via this site to improve the content of our site, to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), for our marketing and research purposes, and for any other purpose specified. In addition, we may make full use of all information acquired through this site that is not in personally identifiable form. If you provide personally identifiable information to this site, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. We may disclose personally identifiable information you provide via this site to other Shimano affiliates worldwide that agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes. 

**Changes**  
If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 1, 2003.
